let questions = [
    {
        "numb": 1,
        "question": "What are some common decision-making models?",
        "answer": "SWOT analysis, Pros and Cons, Decision Matrix",
        "options": [
            "SWOT analysis, Pros and Cons, Decision Matrix",
            "Random selection",
            "Ignoring each other",
            "No idea"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 2,
        "question": "How can group decision-making be improved?",
        "answer": "Effective communication, Collaboration, Data-driven approach",
        "options": [
            "Effective communication, Collaboration, Data-driven approach",
            "Ignoring each other",
            "Making decisions randomly",
            "Hoping for the best"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 3,
        "question": "Describe a situation where effective decision-making positively impacted a group.",
        "answer": "Answers may vary",
        "options": [
            "Answers may vary",
            "No impact at all",
            "Made the situation worse",
            "Indecisiveness prevailed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 4,
        "question": "What are the key elements of effective communication?",
        "answer": "Clear message, Active listening, Feedback",
        "options": [
            "Clear message, Active listening, Feedback",
            "Ignoring each other",
            "Talking without any purpose",
            "Mumbling incoherently"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 5,
        "question": "How can active listening contribute to better group communication?",
        "answer": "Improved understanding, Conflict resolution, Building trust",
        "options": [
            "Improved understanding, Conflict resolution, Building trust",
            "Ignoring each other",
            "Talking over each other",
            "Daydreaming"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 6,
        "question": "Provide an example of a communication strategy that enhances transparency in a group.",
        "answer": "Regular updates, Open forums, Honest feedback",
        "options": [
            "Regular updates, Open forums, Honest feedback",
            "Keeping everyone in the dark",
            "Spreading rumors",
            "Communicating through secret codes"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 7,
        "question": "Describe different leadership styles and their applications.",
        "answer": "Autocratic, Democratic, Transformational",
        "options": [
            "Autocratic, Democratic, Transformational",
            "Ignoring the team",
            "Dictatorship",
            "Anarchy"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 8,
        "question": "How can effective communication contribute to leadership success?",
        "answer": "Clear directives, Team motivation, Conflict resolution",
        "options": [
            "Clear directives, Team motivation, Conflict resolution",
            "Ignoring the team",
            "Confusing everyone with unclear instructions",
            "Leading by intimidation"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 9,
        "question": "Provide an example of successful team motivation by a leader.",
        "answer": "Recognition, Incentives, Setting clear goals",
        "options": [
            "Recognition, Incentives, Setting clear goals",
            "Ignoring the team's efforts",
            "Demotivating the team",
            "Setting unrealistic goals"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 10,
        "question": "What are common sources of conflicts in a group?",
        "answer": "Differences in goals, Communication breakdown, Personality clashes",
        "options": [
            "Differences in goals, Communication breakdown, Personality clashes",
            "Everyone agreeing all the time",
            "No communication at all",
            "Magical harmony with no conflicts"
        ]
    }
]

export default questions
